A Finding Aid to the Betty Parsons Gallery records and personal papers, circa 1920-1991, bulk 1946-1983, in the Archives of American Art AAA.parsbett
Archives of American Art
- Artists Files, 1935-1983; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 51, and OV 53; 17.8 linear feet)
  - Weber, Hugo - Sales and Expenses, 1954-1960 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Weber, Hugo - Announcements, 1951-1959 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Weber, Hugo - Clippings, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Weber, Hugo - Film-Painting Project, 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Weber, Hugo - Photographs, Artist at Work, 1951, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Weber, Hugo - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1960; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Werthmann, Friederich, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Werthmann, Friederich - Photographs, Works of Art, 1963-1967; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Wilson, Charles, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Wilson, Charles - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1962-1967; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Wolfson, Sidney, 1958-1971; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 53-54)
  - Wolfson, Sidney - Photographs, circa 1972; (Partially scanned) (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - el Yacoubi, Ahmed ben Driss, 1951-1953; (Partially scanned) (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Biographical Material, circa 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Correspondence, 1957-1974, 1983; (5 folders) (Box 18, Folder 2-6)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Writings about Artist, circa 1958-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Worcester Art Museum Exhibition (November 2, 1965 - January 2, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Youngerman, Jack - M.I.T. Exhibition (January 10 - February 6, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Phillips Gallery Exhibition (1968), 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Price Lists and Appraisals, 1958-1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Sales and Expenses, 1958-1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Mailing List, circa 1958-1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1970; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Announcements and Catalogs, Duplicates, 1960-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Clippings, 1959-1977 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Lists of Photographs, circa 1958-1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Photographs, Artist and Studio, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Photographs, Installations, 1961, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1958-1974; (Not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Slides, Works of Art and Installations, circa 1958-1974; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Silkscreen for Poster, 1965; (See OV 53) (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Biographical Material, circa 1945-1952 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Correspondence, 1945-1952; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 26-27)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1945-1952 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Clippings, 1946, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Announcements and Catalogs, 1946-1961 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Photograph, Installation, circa 1945-1952 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Zadkine, Ossip - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1945-1952; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 32-35)
  - Oversize, Bonge, Dusti - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1956-1981; (Not scanned) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Box, Eden - Photographs, Artist, circa 1953-1981; (Scanned with Box 2, F14) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Kent, Adaline - Photographs, Artist's Studio, 1950s; (Scanned with Box 8, F31) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Lindner, Richard - Photograph, Artist, circa 1954-1979; (Scanned with Box 10, F8) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Lindner, Richard - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1954-1979; (Not scanned) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Pollock, Jackson - Clippings, 1949-1982; (Scanned with Box 13, F22) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Oversize, Chryssa - Correspondence, 1960-1964; (Scanned with Box 2, F41) (Box OV 53)
  - Oversize, Rosen, Jim, 1977-1978; (Scanned with Box 15, F44) (Box OV 53)
  - Oversize, Youngerman, Jack - Silkscreen for Poster, 1965; (Scanned with Box 18, F24) (Box OV 53)
- Exhibition Files, 1941-1983; Series 2; (Boxes 18-21,51, OV 54; 3.6 linear feet)
  Exhibition files primarily document the gallery's infrequent group or themed exhibitions, and the general administration of exhibitions. Also found are files for exhibitions Parsons organized for other galleries and institutions, and for the short-lived Section Eleven Gallery, an adjunct to the Betty Parsons Gallery that focused on new artists. While some exhibition material related to solo exhibitions can be found here, most of the exhibition material related to one-man/person exhibitions are found in the artists files.
  Exhibitions of particular note for which there are files in this series include The Ideographic Picture, which was organized by Barnett Newman and included his work, as well as that of Pietro Lazzari, Boris Margo, Ad Reinhardt, Mark Rothko, Theodoros Stamos, and Clyfford Still.
  The Exhibition Files series is arranged into six subseries:
  2.1: Group Exhibitions, 1944-1983
  2.2: Loan Exhibitions, 1949-1979
  2.3: Section Eleven Exhibitions, 1958-1961
  2.4: General Exhibition Files, 1941-1983
  2.5: Announcements and Catalogs, 1943-1983
  2.6: Guest Books, 1969-1983
  This series has been mostly scanned in its entirety, except for duplicates and photographs of works of art. Photographs of exhibition installations have been scanned.
  - Group Exhibitions, 1944-1983; 2.1
    Files consist of correspondence, notes, lists, schedules, loan receipts, shipping invoices, press releases, announcements, catalogs, clippings, and photographs, related to group exhibitions at the Betty Parsons Gallery, beginning with the first one, Northwest Coast Indian Painting in 1946 and ending with the planned memorial exhibition, "Betty Parsons and Her Artists/Works on Paper," which was ultimately cancelled.
    Files are arranged chronologically according to the year of exhibition, represented by the first date listed for each file entry. The span dates at the end of each file entry represent the date range of material within the folder(s).
    - Northwest Coast Indian Painting (1946), 1946-1947; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 36-37)
    - Northwest Coast Indian Painting (1946), Printed Material, 1944-1946 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Northwest Coast Indian Painting (1946), Photographs, circa 1946; (Not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - The Ideographic Picture (1947), 1947-1949, 1967, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Ten Years (1955), 1955-1956; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 41-42)
    - Ten Years (1955), Photographs, Installations, circa 1955 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Ten Years (1955), Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1955; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 44-45)
    - Paintings for Unlimited Space (1958-1959), (Partially scanned) (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Amlash Sculpture from Iran (1963), 1963-1977; (4 folders) (Box 18, Folder 47-50)
    - Amlash Sculpture from Iran (1963), Printed Material, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Amlash Sculpture from Iran (1963), Photographs, circa 1963; (2 folders; partially scanned) (Box 18, Folder 52-53)
    - Toys by Artists (1963-1964), (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Toys by Artists (1963-1964), Printed Material, circa 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Toys by Artists (1963-1964), Photographs, circa 1963; (Partially scanned) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Pattern Art (1966) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Pattern Art (1966), Photographs, circa 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Four British Painters (1967) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Four British Painters (1967), Printed Material, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Four British Painters (1967), Photographs, circa 1967; (Not scanned) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - The World of the Zoo (1969) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The World of the Zoo (1969), Photographs, (Partially scanned) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Reductive Vision (1969) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Group Sculpture Show (1970), Photograph (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - New Talent (1973), 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - New Talent Festival (1974), (3 folders) (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
    - Group Exhibition (1978), Photographs (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Group Show (1979-1980), circa 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Group Exhibition (1982), 1982-1983; (2 folders; slides not scanned) (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
    - Painting (1983), (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
    - Painting (1983), Slides, circa 1983; (Not scanned) (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Betty Parsons and Her Artists / Works on Paper (1983, canceled) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Loan Exhibitions, 1949-1979; 2.2
    Files consist of a wide variety of materials, such as correspondence, notes, lists, schedules, loan receipts, shipping invoices, press releases, announcements, catalogs, clippings, and photographs, relating to exhibitions in other galleries or institutions organized by Betty Parsons and/or for which the gallery loaned artwork.
    Files are arranged chronologically according to the year of exhibition, represented by the first date listed for each file heading. The span dates at the end of each file heading represent the date range of material within the folder(s).
    - Paintings and Sculpture by Walter Murch and Adaline Kent (1950: Art Center Association, Louisville, Kentucky and Southbend Art Association, South Bend, Indiana), 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - An Exhibition of Contemporary Religious Art (1953: The Church of the Ascension, New York City) (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - The Artists' Vision (1958: Signa Gallery, East Hampton, New York) (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - ART:USA:58 (Madison Square Garden, New York, New York), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - American Abstract Painters (1961: Arthur Tooth and Sons, London, England), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Four American Painter (1962: Moulton Gallery, London, England), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Seattle World's Fair (1962), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Salon International de Galleries-Pilotes (2nd: 1966: Lausanne, Switzerland), 1965-1967; (6 folders; see also box 51) (Box 19, Folder 33-38)
    - Documenta (4th: 1968: Kassel, Germany), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Barbara Chase-Riboud (1973: Indianapolis Art Museum and Detroit Art Institute) (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - New York: The Last Ten Years (1979: Otis Art Institute of Parsons Design School, Los Angeles, California), (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 41-42)
    - New York: The Last Ten Years (1979: Otis Art Institute of Parsons Design School, Los Angeles, California), Photographs, circa 1979; (Not scanned) (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Oversize, Salon International de Galleries-Pilotes (2nd: 1966: Lausanne, Switzerland), 1965-1967; (Scanned with Box 19, F38) (Box 51 (sol))
  - Section Eleven Exhibitions, 1958-1961; 2.3
    Files consist of correspondence, notes, lists, schedules, loan receipts, shipping invoices, press releases, announcements, catalogs, clippings, and photographs, relating to various group exhibitions held in the Section Eleven Gallery, which operated for a short time, from 1958-1961, as an adjunct to the Betty Parsons Gallery and showcased the work of new artists.
    - Opening, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - New Names (December 20, 1960 - January 7, 1961), 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - New Names (December 20, 1960 - January 7, 1961), Photographs, circa 1960; (Not scanned) (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Various Exhibitions, 1958-1961; (4 folders) (Box 19, Folder 47-50)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1958-1961; (3 folders) (Box 19, Folder 51-53)
  - General Exhibition Files, 1941-1983; 2.4
    Files consist of materials relating to the general planning, production, and administration of exibitions, as well as sales relating to exhibitions. Includes are artists biographies, exhibition schedules, price lists, and other lists. The bulk of the documentation relating to solo exhibitions of particular artists can be found amongst the artist files.
    - Exhibition Lists, Schedules, and Price Lists, 1950-1980 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Group Exhibition Price Lists, 1950-1959 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Group Exhibition Price Lists, 1960-1969 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Group Exhibition Price Lists, 1970-1979 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Group Exhibition Price Lists, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Solo Exhibition Price Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Solo Exhibition Price Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Solo Exhibition Price Lists, 1974-1978 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Price Lists for Exhibition Posters, 1960s (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Lists of Gallery Artists, 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Lists of Artists Represented, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, General List, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, A-B, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, C-F, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, G, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, H, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, J-M, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, O-P, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, R-S, circa 1947-1983 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, T, circa 1947-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Biographies of Gallery Artists, V-Z, circa 1947-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Chronology (including Wakefield Gallery and Mortimer Brandt Gallery), before 1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition List (by artist and title of show), circa 1960 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1941-1950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1954-1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1960-1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Announcements and Catalogs, 1943-1983; 2.5
    Found here are exhibition announcements and catalogs, and a few exhibition posters, for the Betty Parsons Gallery. Exhibition announcements and catalogs can also be found amongst the artists files.
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1946-1950 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1950-1956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Exhibition Announcements, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Exhibition and Other Announcements, Betty Parsons Gallery, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Posters, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1962-1972; (See OV 54) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Other Galleries, 1958-1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Oversize, Exhibition Posters, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1951-1972; (Scanned with Box 20, F20) (Box OV 54)
  - Guest Books, 1969-1983; 2.6
    Guest books contain signatures and comments from visitors to exhibitions at the Betty Parsons Gallery. There is no guest book for 1977.
    - Guest Book, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Guest Book, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Guest Books, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 24-25)
    - Guest Book, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Guest Book, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Guest Book, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Guest Book, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Guest Book, 1976 March-October (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Guest Book, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Guest Book, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Guest Book, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Guest Book, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Guest Book, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Guest Book, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Files, 1941-1983; Series 3; (Boxes 21-24, 52; 3.7 linear feet)
  This series consists of the incoming and outgoing correspondence of the gallery - some of it created by Betty Parsons and some of it by her gallery assistants (Jock Truman and others). It is with various institution and museum officials, art dealers, artists, researchers, collectors. The correspondence series also includes telephone and address books and gallery logs of internal memoranda.
  This series has been scanned in its entirety.
  The correspondence is arranged into five subseries:
  3.1: Institutions and Dealers, 1945-1982
  3.2: Individuals and Collectors, 1941-1982
  3.3: Publishers, Newspapers and Magazines, 1946-1978
  3.4: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1983
  3.5: Gallery Logs and Telephone and Address Books, circa 1978-1981
  - Institutions and Dealers, 1945-1982; 3.1
    Files consist of correspondence with museums, galleries, dealers, colleges and universities, arts organizations, and associations. Correspondence typically relates to the general operations of the gallery, including loans, sales, prices, appraisals, conservation, damages, shipping, insurance, exhibitions, and requests for information about artists. requests for photographs, and slides, shipping,, including promotion, exhibition, and sale of work by gallery artists.
    Files are arranged alphabetically according to the name of the institution or the surname of the individual. When the name of a business or institution also represents the name of an individual, the file is arranged by the name of the business. For example, correspondence with the Sidney Janis Gallery is filed under "S".
    - A, 1947-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      A.M. Sachs Gallery
      A.P.F. Inc.
      Acme Van Co, Inc.
      Adler Gallery
      Albany Institute of History and Art
      Alcoa Steamship Company
      American Abstract Artists
      American Academy in Rome
      American Academy of Arts and Letters
      American West
      Amerika-Haus Tubingen
      Amherst College
      Andre Emmerich Gallery
      Architectural League of New York
      Archives of American Art
      ART:USA:59
      The Art Gallery
      Ariete Grafica
      Arnot Art Museum
      Artists Equity Association
      The Artist's Gallery
      Association for the Advancement of American Art, Inc.
    - Addison Gallery of American Art, 1949-1959 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Akron Art Institute, 1951-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1946-1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1948-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The American University, 1947-1954 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Art Association of Newport, 1952, 1969-1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Art Gallery of Ontario (formerly Art Gallery of Toronto), 1949-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1947-1977; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
    - Arthur Tooth and Sons (London, England), 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Arts Club of Chicago, 1952-1974 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - The Arts Council of Great Britain, 1966-1977 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Atlanta Art Association, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Axiom Gallery (London, England), 1965-1969; (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
    - B, 1948-1981; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
      B.R. Kornblatt Gallery
      Baldwin Kingrey
      Ball State Teachers College
      Barnard College
      Bayonne Jewish Community Center
      Behr Corporation
      Belvedere Gallery
      Betty Mclean Gallery
      Bianchini Gallery
      Bineth Gallery of Fine Arts
      Birmingham Museum of Art
      Blond Fine Art Limited
      Boston Arts Festival
      Botolph Group, Inc.
      Busch-Reisinger Museum
      Butler Art Museum
      The Byron Gallery
    - B.C. Holland Gallery, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Baltimore Art Museum, 1954-1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Bennington College, 1953, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Brandeis University, 1954-1964 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - The Brooklyn Museum, 1951-1963 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Brooks Memorial Art Gallery (Memphis, TN), 1953-1973 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - C, 1949-1978 (Box 21, Folder 28-29)
      The Campus Gallery (Glasgow, Scotland)
      Canada Council
      Carnegie Institute of Technology
      Carnegie Study of the Arts in the United States
      Cecil Clark Davis Gallery
      Cedar Chest College
      Center for Inter-American Relations
      Central Intelligence Agency
      Central Trust Bank
      Le Centre D'Art
      Century 21 Exposition Inc.
      Chattanooga Art Association
      Choate School
      Chrysler Museum of Norfolk
      Cincinnati Modern Art Society
      City Galerie
      City of New York Department of Parks
      Coe Kerr Gallery Inc.
      Colby College
      Collectors Gallery Inc.
      Colony House
      Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center
      Columbia Museum of Art
      Committee for Economic Development
      Connaissance des Arts
      Contemporary Arts Center (Cincinnati, Ohio)
      Contemporary Arts Museum (Houston, Texas)
      Cooper Gallery
      Cordier and Ekstrom
      Cosme Velho Galleria de Arte
      Cowie Galleries
    - California Palace of Legion of Honor, 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Carnegie Institute, Museum of Art, 1947-1978 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1961-1977 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Collezione Peggy Guggenheim, 1948-1966 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1950-1977 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1945-1972 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Cornell University, 1946-1978 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1950, 1970-1980 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Cusack Gallery, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - D, 1957-1976 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      Dallas Theatre Center
      Daniel Weinberg Gallery
      Dartmouth College
      Davenport Municipal Art Gallery
      David Mirvish Gallery
      Delaware Art Center
      Design Students Association
      Devorah Sherman Gallery
      Djuara Limited
      Drew University
      Dreyfuss, Caril E.
      Dryden Associates, Inc.
      Dwan Gallery
    - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1948, 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - David Hendricks Gallery, 1970-1976 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Dayton Art Institute, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - De Cordova Museum, 1965-1975 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1949-1969 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Des Moines Art Center, 1950-1968 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1950-1975 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Dilexi Gallery, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - E, 1952-1975 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      Editions Hyperion
      Eleanor Rigelhaupt Gallery
      Ernest Raboff Gallery
      Ernst de Jong Studios Ateljees
      Everett Elin Gallery
      Everson Museum of Art
    - Esther Bear Gallery, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - F, 1949-1971 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      Fairhaven College
      Fairmount Park Association
      Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego
      Florida Gulf Coast Art Center
      Florida Technology University
      Ford Foundation
      Fort Wayne Art School and Museum
      Fort Worth Art Association Center
      Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts
      Francis G. Mayer Art Slides
      Frank Perls Gallery